pressreleasebootcamp.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy « Press Release Bootcamp

Privacy Policy

IMPORTANT!  
THIS PRIVACY POLICY (“POLICY”) DESCRIBES HOW pressreleasebootcamp.com, owned and operated by Adventure Marketing LLC (“pressreleasebootcamp.com”) PROTECTS, USES AND SHARES ANY INFORMATION WHICH IS PROVIDED BY YOU AT pressreleasebootcamp.com(COLLECTIVELY, THE “SITE”). BY ACCESSING THE SITE, YOU ARE INDICATING THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTOOD AND AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLCY AND OUR TERMS OF SERVICE.  
IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF SERVICE OR OUR PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SITE OR ANY SERVICES OFFERED AT THE SITE.

Your Privacy  
Your privacy is important to us at Adventure Marketing LLC. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. You agree to agree to these policies by virtue of using our website in a way that leads to you providing us with personal information.

Anti-Spam Policy  
The following describes the Anti-Spam Policy for our pressreleasebootcamp.com website.

What Is Spam?  
Spam is unsolicited email, also known as junk mail (received via email), or UCE (Unsolicited Commercial Email). Virtually all of us have opened the inbox of an email account and found emails from an unknown sender. By sending email only to those who have requested to receive it, we at Adventure Marketing LLC are following accepted permission-based email guidelines.

What About The Laws Against Spam?  
They exist. However, as with any body of laws, any individual State spam statutes can and will vary. The spam laws of each State can not only vary, but also have different definitions of unsolicited commercial email. Additionally, there may be various federal agencies keeping track of spam, including the Federal Trade Commission (FTC). At the Federal level, the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 promulgates some attempt at a coherent and unified approach to unsolicited commercial email. Ultimately, it would be difficult to enforce spam law violations on any consistent or pervasive basis, so your own vigilance is your own best first line of defense. Beyond that, we protect you by ensuring that you are 100% in control of whether or not you ever hear from Adventure Marketing LLC by email initially or in the future, as detailed in our “No Tolerance” policy below.

Our No Tolerance Anti-Spam Policy  
WE HAVE A NO TOLERANCE SPAM POLICY. We do not email unless someone has filled out an “opt in” form or “webform” expressing an interest in our information or products and/or services, or otherwise directly and proactively requesting it. News of the features and benefits of Membership is spread through advertising, joint venture marketing, and word of mouth, so we are only building relationship with folks who wish to learn more about what we have to offer and willingly subscribe to our content and contact through email. You are always completely in control of whether you receive email communication from pressreleasebootcamp.com, and can terminate at any time.

NOTE – Every auto-generated email contains a mandatory unsubscribe link that cannot be removed. Therefore, each communication generated by pressreleasebootcamp.com carries with it the option to “unsubscribe” and never receive another email communication from Adventure Marketing LLC.

State Law & Accompanying Rights  
Please understand that you may have additional rights originating from State laws based on where you live. These State-based rights may augment, strengthen, or otherwise somehow compliment any privacy rights you have inherently or under Federal law. Our policy is to comply fully with the privacy policies of every jurisdiction in which we operate. Accordingly, you are free to use our Contact information to reach us at any time to assert any State rights.

Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, our website will never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18.

Protecting children’s privacy is especially important to us. It is our policy to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and all other applicable laws. Therefore pressreleasebootcamp.com restricts our Site to persons eighteen years or older. YOU MUST BE EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS OR OLDER TO ACCESS THIS SITE. IF YOU ARE UNDER EIGHTEEN YEARS OF AGE, YOU ARE NOT PERMITTED TO ACCESS THIS SITE FOR ANY REASON. DUE TO THE AGE RESTRICTIONS FOR USE OF THIS SITE, NO INFORMATION OBTAINED BY THIS SITE, FALLS WITHIN THE CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT (COPPA) AND IS NOT MONITORED AS DOING SO.

Under our Terms of Service and Conditions of Use, children under 18 are not allowed to use our website and access our services. It is not our intention to offer products or services to minors.

Types of Information that pressreleasebootcamp.com Collects  
pressreleasebootcamp.com collects two different types of information from You when You use the Site. We collect certain types of personally identifiable information from You (“Personal Information”) when You register a member or affiliate account (“Account”). We also collect certain non- personally identifiable, aggregate information from visitors to our Site regardless of whether they create or sign in to an Account (“Traffic Data”).  
Personal Information  
In order to create an Account You will have to provide Personal Information that may include:  
a. name  
b. address  
c. telephone number  
d. billing information (such as a credit card number)  
e. the type of personal computer being used to access the services/IP Address  
f. payment and tax withholding information

Your Personal Information is used to manage Your Account and is not shared with third parties, unless specifically stated otherwise or in special circumstances. In compliance with applicable laws, it is our policy to require only the Personal Information necessary to manage Your Account and enable You to participate in our programs (as applicable, the “Program”). pressreleasebootcamp.com does not condition Your participation in any specific activity on our Site on the disclosure of more information than is reasonably necessary.

Traffic Data  
pressreleasebootcamp.com may also use certain web technologies such as “cookies” to track Your use of our Site. Your browser may have an option that allows You to reject cookies, but doing so may limit Your use of our Site. Usage Information is anonymous and does not personally identify You. In addition, pressreleasebootcamp.com may use web beacons or other tools to measure the effectiveness of, and otherwise manage, our online advertising. These web beacons enable our advertising server to recognize You when You visit the Site and to determine which banner ads bring users to the Site. pressreleasebootcamp.com does not use spyware, adware or any other similarly intrusive software. The Usage Information that pressreleasebootcamp.com collects depends on how You choose to use this Site.

Use of Your Information  
pressreleasebootcamp.com may use Your Personal Information to manage Your Account, such as responding to Your email inquiries or providing You with voluntary customer surveys to helps us to improve the types of products and services we offer to You. In addition, pressreleasebootcamp.com may use Traffic Data to deliver tailored advertisements or joint ventures. For instance, an advertiser or joint venture company tells us the audience they want to reach and provides us an advertisement tailored to the audience. Based upon the aggregated and non-identifying information we have collected, we may then display or send the advertisement to the intended audience. Additionally, pressreleasebootcamp.com may share non-identifying and aggregate information (except as described above), but not Personal Information, with third parties to administer certain co-branded products or services. Finally, pressreleasebootcamp.com may take the information collected in response to customer surveys and combine (or aggregate) it with the responses of other customers to create broader, generic responses to the survey questions (such as gender, age, residence, hobbies, education, employment, industry sector, or other demographic information). This aggregated, non-personally identifying information may be shared with third parties.

Note that any personal information you provide to others apart from us or our vendors is wholly optional. As an example, you might disclose something in a blog post comment. That “private” information is now “public,” and we have no control over that. In like fashion, you sharing information with any other third party not functioning as a service provider to us puts that information beyond our control and becomes subject to the policy that party has in place.

Third Party Websites  
The Site may be hyper-linked to other sites which are not maintained by, or related to, pressreleasebootcamp.com. If You opt to provide information to such web sites, for example, to purchase products and services or register to receive materials, such as a newsletter, catalog or new product and service updates, please be aware that pressreleasebootcamp.com has no control over the third parties’ use of any personal information You provide when placing such an order. Please exercise care when doing so and carefully review such website’s privacy policies before providing any information. If You provide information about someone else, such as a person’s name, address, and phone number, please be aware that such provision may be prohibited by certain laws and that You, and not pressreleasebootcamp.com, are solely responsible for doing so.

Contests  
From time to time, subject to any rules provided at the Site at such time, You may be provided with the opportunity to be entered in a sweepstakes, contest, or other promotion simply by making a purchase from pressreleasebootcamp.com or by providing pressreleasebootcamp.com with personally identifiable information for some other reason or purpose. In such event, pressreleasebootcamp.com may have to supply personally identifiable information of the winners to the third parties such as the entity administering the sweepstakes or contest, so that they can notify the winners

Exclusions  
pressreleasebootcamp.com may disclose Personal Information for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: to credit agencies, collection agencies, merchant database agencies, law enforcement, or to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms Of Service, or other user policies; or to protect our company and our members. We may sell or buy other businesses or entities. In such event, pressreleasebootcamp.com may transfer or assign the information we have collected as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control In such transactions, Your Personal Information may be included in the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors’ rights generally, pressreleasebootcamp.com may not be able to control how Your Personal Information is treated, transferred, or used and Your Personal Information may be included in the transferred assets.

Information-Sharing Disclosures  
Under the laws of some jurisdictions, You may be entitled to request disclosure regarding how pressreleasebootcamp.com shares Your Usage Information with third parties for direct marketing purposes (“Information-Sharing Disclosure”). To the extent required by applicable law, pressreleasebootcamp.com shall provide the Information-Sharing Disclosure to You upon rightful request made in writing to adventuremarketingllc@gmail.com and please include the phrase ” Privacy Request” and Your State of residence in the subject line, the domain name of the Site You are inquiring about, along with Your name, address and email address. If You are entitled to such Information-Sharing Disclosure, pressreleasebootcamp.com will respond to You within thirty days of receiving such a request.

Public Forums  
Please remember that any information You may disclose in any public areas of the Site becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these public areas. pressreleasebootcamp.com cannot and will not be liable or responsible for any disclosure of any information You publish in a public area of the Site.

Social Media Disclosure  
The following describes the Social Media Disclosure for our pressreleasebootcamp.com website.

Social Media Issue  
We live in an interesting time when privacy rights are championed alongside an unprecedented voluntary willingness of people to share their most intimate and superfluous life details with the world, even in places such as our Adventure Marketing LLC website. While apparently benign on the surface, the dangers of unrestrained public disclosure of sensitive information is beginning to surface.

Key social media players are being sued for unauthorized or abusive use/misuse of personal information. Failure to protect and warn are likely going to be focal factors. Lawsuits are filed seeking damages for statements held to be responsible for people’s death or suicide. Bloggers presuming to operate under an unfettered freedom of speech or greater latitude offered to members of the press are losing civil cases for defamation, slander, libel, and so on.

As social media rapidly advances to allow more technologically sophisticated and easy dissemination, the simultaneous fallout of revelation without boundaries is mounting. Thus, a sober approach to the benefits of social media, while sidestepping the perils of imprudent disclosure, can facilitate an enjoyable online experience, without the consequences of excess, in settings such as our own pressreleasebootcamp.com website.

Presence/Scope of Social Media  
You should assume that social media is in use on our Adventure Marketing LLC website. A simple click of a button to endorse a person, product, or service is building a cumulative profile about you, which you should always assume can be discovered by others. Attempting to share a website with someone, whether by direct press of a button or else by email forwarding facilitated on a website, you should assume that this may not stop with the intended recipient, and that this can generate information about you that could be seen by a veritable infinite number of people. Such a domino effect could initiate right here on our pressreleasebootcamp.com website.

Something as simple as a blog comment provides the opportunity for knee-jerk reactions that can become public and may not truly represent a position (at least in strength or severity) that you might hold after a period of more reasoned contemplation. You should also note that the ease of accessing one site through the login credentials of another, or the use of a global login for access to multiple sites can accumulate a dossier on you and your online behavior that may reveal more information to unintended parties than you might realize or want. Any or all of these features could exist on our Adventure Marketing LLC website at one time or another.

These few examples illustrate some possible ways that social media can exist, though it is not an exhaustive list and new technologies will render this list outdated quickly. The objective is to realize the reach of social media, its widespread presence on websites in various forms (including this website), and develop a responsible approach to using it.

Protecting Others  
You should recognize the fact that divulgences made in and on social media platforms on this website and others are rarely constrained just to you. Disclosures are commonly made about group matters that necessarily affect and impact other people. Other disclosures are expressly about third parties, sometimes with little discretion. What can appear funny in one moment can be tragic in the next. And a subtle “public” retaliation can have lifetime repercussions.

Ideal use of social media on our website would confine your disclosures primarily to matters pertaining to you, not others. If in doubt, it’s best to err on the side of non-disclosure. It’s doubtful the disclosure is so meaningful that it cannot be offset by the precaution of acting to protect the best interests of someone who is involuntarily being exposed by your decision to disclose something on our pressreleasebootcamp.com website (or another).

Protecting Yourself  
You should likewise pause to consider the long-term effects of a split-second decision to publicly share private information about yourself on our Adventure Marketing LLC website. Opinions, likes, dislikes, preferences, and otherwise can change. Openly divulging perspectives that you hold today, may conflict with your developing views into the futures. Yet, the “new you” will always stand juxtaposed against the prior declarations you made that are now concretized as part of your public profile. While the contents of your breakfast may hold little long-term impact, other data likewise readily shared can have consequences that could conceivably impact your ability to obtain certain employment or hinder other life experiences and ambitions.

As with sharing information about other people, extreme caution should be used before revealing information about yourself. If in doubt, it’s likely best not to do it. The short term gain, if any, could readily be outweighed by later consequences. Finally, you should note that we are not responsible for removing content once shared, and we may not be able to do so.

Restrictions on Use of Social Media Data  
You, as a visitor to our pressreleasebootcamp.com website, are not permitted to “mine” social media or other platforms contained herein for personal information related to others. Even where people have publicly displayed data, you should not construe that as though you have the liberty to capture, reproduce, or reuse that information. Any use of social media or related platforms on our website are for interactive use only, relevant only during the website visit.

Accuracy of Social Media Data  
As any social media platform is built on user-generated content, you should consider this fact in seeking to determine the authenticity of anything you read. We are not responsible for verifying any user-generated content for accuracy. A best practices policy would be to view all such content as strictly opinion, not fact.

Potential Issues of Liability  
You should also be mindful of the fact that your words could trigger liability for harm caused to others. While you have the right to free speech, you do not have the right to damage other people. Under basic principles of tort law, you are always responsible, personally, for situations where either:

1\. you were required to act, but did not (i.e. – some “duty of care”)  
2\. your were required to refrain from acting, but did not (i.e. – slander, defamation, etc.)

These “sins of omission and commission” could cause problems for you, irrespective of whether you assert you are conducting business under the guise of one or more business entities. Illegal and unethical conduct, when done in the name of a corporation or LLC, is still illegal and unethical conduct. As it is rarely part of a business plan to engage in illegal and unethical conduct, you are doubtfully operating in any official capacity, but rather, perhaps, leveraging that capacity to effectuate personal wrongdoing. You should consult a licensed attorney if you wish legal advice as to the (potential) ramification of your situation or legal problems stemming from this website or another.

Our Commitment to Data Security:  
pressreleasebootcamp.com takes reasonable precautions and has implemented reasonable technical measures intended to protect against the risks of unauthorized access to, erroneous disclosure of, and unlawful interception of Your Personal Information, including by requiring our payment processor to comply with applicable laws and industry standards and by employing Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology supported by most versions of Microsoft Internet Explorer, Netscape Navigator and other popular browsers. Once Your Personal Information is received by pressreleasebootcamp.com, we use commercially reasonable efforts to limit access to Your Personal Information about You to those employees and service providers whom pressreleasebootcamp.com determines need access to that Personal Information to complete Your request and/or other provide offers or opportunities that may be of interest to You. However, even after pressreleasebootcamp.com receives Your Personal Information, pressreleasebootcamp.com cannot guarantee that Your Personal Information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed as a result of a breach of our commercially reasonable efforts or as a result of any other event beyond our reasonable control. Also, please be aware that Your email transmissions and/or other communications to pressreleasebootcamp.com containing Personal Information may be unlawfully intercepted or accessed by third parties and/or this Site may be subject to hostile network attacks or administrative errors. Accordingly, pressreleasebootcamp.com cannot and does not guarantee that Your Personal Information is completely secure and safe from such risks.

FOR THE AVOIDANCE OF DOUBT, WE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM ANY REPRESENTATION OR WARRANTY, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, WITH RESPECT TO ENSURING, GUARANTEEING OR OTHERWISE OFFERING ANY DEFINITIVE PROMISE OF SECURITY IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, PERSONAL INFORMATION OR USAGE INFORMATION.

Where to Direct Questions About Our Privacy Policy  
If You have any questions about this Policy or the practices described herein, You may contact us through the contact information provided on this Site.

CHANGE NOTICE: As with any of our administrative and legal notice pages, the contents of this page can and will change over time. Accordingly, this page could read differently as of your very next visit. These changes are necessitated, and carried out by Adventure Marketing LLC, in order to protect you and our pressreleasebootcamp.com website. If this page is important to you, you should check back frequently as no other notice of changed content will be provided either before or after the change takes effect.

COPYRIGHT WARNING: The legal notices and administrative pages on this website, including this one, have been diligently drafted by an attorney. We at Adventure Marketing LLC have paid to license the use of these legal notices and administrative pages on pressreleasebootcamp.com for your protection and ours. This material may not be used in any way for any reason and unauthorized use is policed via Copyscape to detect violators.

Last updated: January 2013
